好的  行的  不要  帮我订好  我可不要  橘黄色的  这是谁
Yes, yes, no, book it, hate it, orange... Who is this?!
- 丽芙·鲁尼  大明星啊  - 您好
- Liv Rooney, superstar. - Hi.
我真心想见见这位敢同时叫板
Been dying to meet the girl who's got the nerve
莱恩·戈斯林和范·迪赛尔的女孩
to go up against Ryan Gosling and Vin diesel.
我想看看你今天给我们准备了怎样的视觉盛宴
We are dying to see what you have for us today.
记住  这个角色最重要的特点
Now remember, the most important thing
在于这一段台词最后的仰天长啸
is that big howl at the end of your speech.
放松
Really let loose.
你会有充分的时间准备好
Take all the time you need to get ready.
我不想让你赶工
I don't want to rush you.
开始
And action!
成败在此一举了
This was it.
这是我进军大银幕的机会
This was my chance to become a movie star.
以吾之质子之鞭  降汝于膝下
By the sting of my proton whip, I will bring you to your knees,
以吾为汝之克星
for I am your doom.
吾乃群狼之首
I am wolf.
吾乃特利斯坦·莱肯
I am Tristan Lycanth.
然后和
And?!
对哦  结束
Oh, right. And scene.
我要的狼嚎呢
No, where was my howl?
这没有狼嚎可不行
I need to hear a howl.
从头再来一遍吧
Let's try it again from the top.
好的
Okay.
对了  确认一下  这次不要狼嚎  对吧
Um, just to be clear, though, this is gonna be without the howl?
这次我要你嚎叫出来
With the howl.
对哦
Right.